[
    {
        "question":"shelf",
        "answer":"ves"
    },
    {
        "question":"bench",
        "answer":"es"
    },
    {
        "question":"pencil",
        "answer": "s"
    },
    {
        "question":"pupppy",
        "answer": "ies"
    },
    {
        "question":"toy",
        "answer": "s"
    },
    {
        "question":"box",
        "answer": "es"
    },
    {
        "question":"leaf",
        "answer": "ves"
    },
    {
        "question":"story",
        "answer": "ies"
    },
    {
        "question":"wife",
        "answer": "ves"
    },
    {
        "question":"potato",
        "answer": "es"
    }
]